Guide to the Yale Events and Activities Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Photographs of events and activities, 1852-1974; Series I
  - Sterling Memorial Library
    - "Red China" Collection, 1951 (Box 62, Folder 972)
    - Rilke, Rainer Maria, Collection, 1957 (Box 62, Folder 973)
    - Rogers, Bruce, Collection, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 974)
    - St. Thomas Aquinas, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 975)
    - Schidorsky, Bernard - Hebrew Librarian, 1957 (Box 62, Folder 976)
    - Southport Library Collection, 1952 (Box 63, Folder 977)
    - Staff Librarian, 1956-1966 (Box 63, Folder 978)
    - Stevenson, Robert Lewis, Collection, 1951 (Box 63, Folder 979)
    - Stimson, Henry, Papers, 1952-1959 (Box 63, Folder 980)
    - Streeter Texas Collection, 1957 (Box 63, Folder 981)
    - Theater Guild files, 1958 (Box 63, Folder 982)
    - Tibetan Collection, 1951-1967 (Box 63, Folder 983)
    - Van Vechten, Carl, Gift, 1955 (Box 63, Folder 984)
    - Voice Library, 1949 (Box 63, Folder 985)
    - Walpole Papers, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 986)
    - Whythorne, Thomas, Autobiography, 1956 (Box 63, Folder 987)
    - Wing, Donald G., "The Short-Title Catalogue 1651-1700", 1952 (Box 63, Folder 988)
    - Yung Wing Collection, 1954 (Box 64, Folder 989)
    - Ziskind Collection, Greek, 1957 (Box 64, Folder 990)
  - "Stinky", a dog (Box 64, Folder 991)
  - Street Hall (Box 64, Folder 992)
  - Strike
    - Custodians (Box 64, Folder 993)
    - New York Times (Box 64, Folder 994)
  - Student Agencies (Box 64, Folder 995)
  - Student Democratic Society (Box 64, Folder 996)
  - Studying (Box 64, Folder 997)
  - Summer
    - Conferences, 1956 (Box 64, Folder 998)
    - Programs, 1963-1971 (Box 64, Folder 999 - 1002)
  - Swimming, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 1003)
  - Symphony, John Maulbri, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 1004)
  - Synanon (Box 64, Folder 1005)
  - Taft Hotel (Box 64, Folder 1006)
  - Tenure Crisis, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 1007)
  - "There's A Story Being Told About Yale" Exhibition, 1948-1952 (Box 64, Folder 1008)
  - Tiddlywinks (Box 65, Folder 1009)
  - Time Magazine (Box 65, Folder 1010)
  - Tombs, Senior Societies (Box 65, Folder 1011)
  - Towers, 1948-1969 (Box 65, Folder 1012)
  - Towing Cars (Box 65, Folder 1013)
  - Town-Gown, including U.S. Grant Foundation, 1965-1967 (Box 65, Folder 1014 - 1015)
  - Transitional Year Program (Box 65, Folder 1016)
  - Treason (Box 65, Folder 1017)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1954-1966 (Box 65, Folder 1018)
  - Turbine car (Box 65, Folder 1019)
  - United Restaurant Gallery (Box 65, Folder 1020)
  - University
    - Council, 1948-1965 (Box 65, Folder 1021)
    - Development, 1955-1964 (Box 65, Folder 1022 - 1024)
    - Health, Department of (DUH) (Box 65, Folder 1025)
  - "Up With People" (Box 65, Folder 1026)
  - Urban
    - Redevelopment (Box 65, Folder 1027)
    - Studies, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 1028)
  - Vacations, student (Box 65, Folder 1029)
  - Veterans, Korean War, 1952 (Box 66, Folder 1030)
  - Vidiots (Box 66, Folder 1031)
  - Vietnamese students (Box 66, Folder 1032)
  - Vietnam War, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 1033)
  - Vineland
    - Map, Lief Erickson, 1955-1965 (Box 66, Folder 1034)
    - Party (Box 66, Folder 1035)
  - Visitors
    - Distinguished A-Z, 1959-1968 (Box 66, Folder 1036 - 1085)
    - From Yale, 1955-1961 (Box 67, Folder 1086)
    - To Yale
      - A-M, 1950-1974 (Box 67, Folder 1087 - 1091)
      - N-Z, 1953-1973 (Box 68, Folder 1092 - 1094)
      - Miscellaneous, 1957-1958 (Box 68, Folder 1095)
  - Vista, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 1096)
  - Voices Incorporated, Negro acting group (Box 68, Folder 1097)
  - Voting, Hearing for lowering voting age in Connecticut to 18 (Box 68, Folder 1098)
  - Waiters, Yale (Box 68, Folder 1099)
  - Wallace, George, demonstration, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 1100)
  - Watches, time (Box 68, Folder 1101)
  - Wiffenpoofs, 40th Anniversary, 1949 (Box 68, Folder 1102)
  - Wilson Fellows (Box 68, Folder 1103)
  - Wooster Square Project, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 1104)
  - World War II
    - Army Air Force Technical Training Command (AAFTTC), 1944-1946 (Box 68, Folder 1105 - 1106)
    - Army Training Schools (ASTP), 1944 (Box 68, Folder 1107 - 1108)
    - Barracks, 1940s (Box 68, Folder 1109)
    - Bureau of Military Training Information, BMI, 1942 (Box 69, Folder 1110)
    - Civil Affairs Training School (CATS), 1944 (Box 69, Folder 1111)
    - Chinese Classes, and Chinese Press, 1945 (Box 69, Folder 1112)
    - Draft registration, 1940 (Box 69, Folder 1113)
    - First Aid, Air Raid, 1940s (Box 69, Folder 1114)
    - Japanese Classes (Box 69, Folder 1115)
    - Legion of Merit, 1945 (Box 69, Folder 1116)
    - Military Intelligence School (MIS), 1945 (Box 69, Folder 1117)
    - Navy Chaplains' School, 1940s (Box 69, Folder 1118)
    - Quonset Huts, 1940s (Box 69, Folder 1119)
    - Reserve Officers Training Corps (ROTC), 1940-45 (Box 69, Folder 1120)
    - Staff Officers School for Asiatic Studies (SOSAS), 1945 (Box 69, Folder 1121)
    - S.S. "Yale Victory", 1945 (Box 69, Folder 1122)
    - VE Day, 1945 (Box 69, Folder 1123)
    - V-J, 1940s (Box 69, Folder 1124)
    - V-12, 1940s (Box 69, Folder 1125)
    - Veterans
      - Classes, in, 1945 (Box 69, Folder 1126)
      - Two World Wars, in, 1945 (Box 69, Folder 1127)
      - Wives, 1940s (Box 69, Folder 1128)
    - War Gardens, 1944 (Box 70, Folder 1129)
    - Yale Studies for Returning Service Men Program, 1945 (Box 70, Folder 1130 - 1131)
  - WTIC Radio Bazaar, 1950 (Box 70, Folder 1132)
  - WYBC, Yale Broadcasting Company, 1960-1962 (Box 70, Folder 1133 - 1134)
  - WYBC - TV, 1953 (Box 70, Folder 1135 - 1136)
  - Yale
    - Aviation Club, 1965 (Box 70, Folder 1137)
    - Bowl (Box 70, Folder 1138)
    - Center for British Art, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 1139)
      See also: British Art Center, box 13, folder 214.
    - China,Yale-in-, 1955-1967 (Box 70, Folder 1140)
    - College, including college seminars, 1963-1972 (Box 71, Folder 1141)
    - Corporation (Box 71, Folder 1142)
      See also: Corporation, The Yale, box 20, folder 311.
    - Daily Banquet (Box 71, Folder 1143)
    - Daily News, 1942-1966 (Box 71, Folder 1144)
    - Daily News Executives (Box 71, Folder 1145)
    - Interprets the News Program, 1953 (Box 71, Folder 1146 - 1147)
    - Literature, 125th Anniversary, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 1148)
    - Mathematics Building, Proposed, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1149)
    - Non-Faculty Action Committee (YNFAC) (Box 71, Folder 1150)
    - Pharmacy (Box 71, Folder 1151)
    - Political Union, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1152)
    - Record (Box 71, Folder 1153)
    - Reports, 1959-1968 (Box 71, Folder 1154)
    - Unions (Box 71, Folder 1155)
    - University Community Development (YUCD), 1965 (Box 71, Folder 1156)
    - University -- Governance, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 1157)
    - University Press (Box 71, Folder 1158 - 1159)
      - Anniversary, 50th, Sizer rug, 1958 (Box 71, Folder 1160)
      - Building Dedication, 1960 (Box 71, Folder 1161)
      - Day, George Parmly, 80th Birthday, 1956 (Box 72, Folder 1162)
      - National Library Week, 1960 (Box 72, Folder 1163)
      - Publications, 1941-1969 (Box 72, Folder 1164 - 1166)
      - Publications Committee, 1950 (Box 72, Folder 1167)
      - Staff, 1956-1964 (Box 72, Folder 1168)
      - Visitors, 1956-1965 (Box 72, Folder 1169 - 1170)
    - Station -- Postmaster retirement, 1956-1965 (Box 72, Folder 1171)
  - Yankee Doodle Restaurant (Box 72, Folder 1172)
  - Yoga (Box 72, Folder 1173)
  - Yogi (Box 72, Folder 1174)
  - Yorkside Restaurant (Box 72, Folder 1175)
  - Youth Forum (Box 72, Folder 1176)
  - Zoology
    - Chick, transplanted head, 1958 (Box 72, Folder 1177)
    - Fish, nerves (Box 72, Folder 1178)
    - "Horseshoe Crab" - Waterman, Talbot H., 1952 (Box 72, Folder 1179)
    - Micro-Manometer, 1949 (Box 72, Folder 1180)
    - Paramecia Aurelia, 1958 (Box 72, Folder 1181)
    - Spiders, Petrunkevitch, Alexander, 1945 (Box 72, Folder 1182)
    - Students, 1958 (Box 72, Folder 1183)
    - Trinkhaus, J. P., 1958-1959 (Box 72, Folder 1184)
  - Subject index
    - A-HOR (Box 73)
    - HOT-STR (Box 74)
    - STU-Z (Box 75)
- Photographs of events and activities, 1950-circa 1994; Series II
  - General
    - Afro-American Studies (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Afro American Cultural Center (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Art School
      - Rollins Fellowship, 1985-1988 (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - Students, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - Student Exhibitions (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - Students and Faculty (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Astronomy (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Auditing Dept, Group photo, 1990 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Aviation, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Batell Chapel, Organ Renovations, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Batell Chapel, 100th Anniversary/Restoration and re-dedication (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Bicentennial of the U.S., 1976 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Blood Drive, 1980-1987 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Botany, Plant cloning, Arthur Galston (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Career Services, Susan Hauser, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Center for International Studies (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Computers, Students, Labs (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Computers, Labs, Hardware (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Computer Science (Box 77, Folder 19)
    - Cancer Center, Mobile Mammography Unit (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - Cuba, The Cuban Dialogue, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 21)
    - Conference Services, 1981-1985 (Box 77, Folder 22)
    - Campus Mail, New Facilities, 1984 (Box 77, Folder 23)
    - Chaplaincy Group, 1989 (Box 77, Folder 24)
    - Charities, Children's Book Collection, 1988 (Box 77, Folder 25)
    - Daedalus Flight Project, 1986 (Box 77, Folder 26)
    - Debating Team, World Championship, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 27)
    - Christmas, Parade of the Comestibles, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 28)
    - Dance, Vintage Dance Workshop, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 29)
    - Dining Halls, Commons, Bakery, Butcher (Box 77, Folder 30)
    - Dining Halls, Students (Box 77, Folder 31)
    - Directed Studies, (February 1982): A Measure of gruel: It's good for the intellect, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 32)
    - Disabilities, Resource Office (Box 77, Folder 33)
    - Drug Control, Dr. Herbert Kleber, 1989 (Box 77, Folder 34)
    - Earth Day (Box 77, Folder 35)
    - Economics, Blackboards of the late Tjalling Koopmans (Box 77, Folder 36)
    - Economic Growth Center, Faculty and Students (Box 77, Folder 37)
    - Economic Growth Center, Brochure, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 38)
    - Elizabethan Club, 1986 December (Box 78, Folder 39)
    - Elderly Nutrition Project, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 40)
    - Energy, "The Politics of Energy" (Box 78, Folder 41)
    - Energy Conservation (Box 78, Folder 42)
    - Energy Booklet, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 43)
    - Energy Conservation Booklet, Kill-a-Watt Contest (Box 78, Folder 44)
    - Energy conservation, recycling, Sun Day, etc. (Box 78, Folder 45)
    - Enlightenment, 4th International Congress, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 46)
    - English Daily Themes, 1983 (Box 78, Folder 47)
    - Facilities Management, Check Presentation, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 48)
    - Faculty Spouses (Box 78, Folder 49)
    - Fast, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 50)
    - Fellowships, Mellon, Sloan, Libby Zion (Box 78, Folder 51)
    - Film Study Center (Box 78, Folder 52)
    - Film, PBS Documentary, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 53)
    - Flagpole in Hewitt Quadrangle (Box 78, Folder 54)
    - GESO, Budget Cuts Rally (Box 79, Folder 55)
    - Graduate Fellows (Box 79, Folder 56)
    - Glaziers, Law School Windows, 1987 (Box 79, Folder 57)
    - Gnosticism Conference, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 58)
    - Graduate and Professional Assembly
      - 1976- 1987 (Box 79, Folder 59)
      - 1983-1985 (Box 79, Folder 60)
      - 1986-1988 (Box 79, Folder 61)
      - 1989-1991 (Box 79, Folder 62)
    - Ulysses S. Grant Foundation (Box 79, Folder 63)
    - Grove Street Cemetery, (June 1986): The Grove Street Cemetery has an interesting history; (October 21, 1983): Life and Death at the Grove Street Cemetery, 1983, 1986 (Box 79, Folder 64)
    - Halloween (Box 79, Folder 65)
    - Handicapped Facilities: The handicapped: Yale, 1985 February (Box 79, Folder 66)
    - Hillel, Chicken Soup Brigade: Light and Verity: Can't beat it cold, 1988 May (Box 79, Folder 67)
    - George Pierson, Branford Green Monument, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 68)
    - Honorary Degree, "Smokey Joe" Joe Wood (Box 79, Folder 69)
    - Howland Memorial Prize (Box 79, Folder 70)
    - Human Relations, Korean Symposium (Box 79, Folder 71)
    - Human Resources (Box 79, Folder 72)
      - Long Service Awards
        - 1976-1985 (Box 80, Folder 73)
        - 1986-1990 (Box 80, Folder 74)
      - Training Program (Box 80, Folder 75)
    - Institution for Social and Policy Studies (Box 80, Folder 76)
    - Instrument Center (Box 80, Folder 77)
    - Italian Exhibit (Box 80, Folder 78)
    - Internships, Blue Jay Cleaners, New Haven Register (Box 80, Folder 79)
    - Jackals, Patricia Moehlman (Box 80, Folder 80)
    - Judaic Studies (Box 80, Folder 81)
    - Kosher Kitchen (Box 80, Folder 82)
    - Language Laboratory, (December 1986): Light and Verity: Touch screen lab for language study; (April 1989): Light and Verity: French couse a hit, 1986, 1989 (Box 80, Folder 83)
    - Master of Arts in Teaching Program, 1954 (Box 81, Folder 84)
    - Memorial Hall, Memorial Tables (Box 81, Folder 85)
    - The Yale Microscope (Box 81, Folder 86)
    - Mory's Cup: Light and Verity: Mory's concocts a cup for the clear-eyed, 1992 April (Box 81, Folder 87)
    - Music Department, Yale College (Box 81, Folder 88)
    - National Humanities Institute (Box 81, Folder 89)
    - National Sciences Foundation, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 90)
    - Olympics, symposium, (August 1980): The USOC, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 91)
    - Organs, Woolsey Hall, Newberry Organ (Box 81, Folder 92)
    - Organist (Box 81, Folder 93)
    - Parcourse Fitness Trail (Box 81, Folder 94)
    - Parliamentory History, Center for: The farmers: forefathers, 1987 December (Box 81, Folder 95)
    - Physical Plant, Maintenance (Box 81, Folder 96)
    - Pope Memorial Park (Box 81, Folder 97)
    - Poynter fellowship
      - Symposium, 1979 January 18 (Box 81)
      - Does Baseball Have a Future?, 1986 February (Box 81)
        Participants: Peter Ueberroth, Roger Angell, Peter Gammons, A. Bartlett Giamatti.
      - Brown, Tina, 1986 (Box 81)
      - Walker, Kenneth, 1986
      - Ross, Brian and Ira Silverman, 1987 October (Box 81)
      - Bode, Ken, Jack W. Germond, Robert J. Leeney, Robin Toner, Jack White, 1988 (Box 81)
    - Professorship, Housum, Bird White (Box 81, Folder 98)
    - Puerto Rican Cultural Center (Box 81, Folder 99)
    - Residential Colleges, 50th Anniversary, (Thursday, October 27, 1983): Yale Salutes 50th year residential colleges; (December 1983): A fifty-year review of the college system (Box 81, Folder 100 - 101)
    - Russia Student Exchange (Box 81, Folder 102)
    - Russia: Light and Verity: Fall visit a first for Russian chemists, 1987 December (Box 81, Folder 103)
    - Seminars (Box 82, Folder 104)
    - Slavic Chorus/Slavic Festival (Box 82, Folder 105)
    - Smoking Policy (Box 82, Folder 106)
    - Solidarity (Box 82, Folder 107)
    - Spanish-Portugese Correl (Box 82, Folder 108)
    - Speaking Bureaus, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 109)
    - Special Students, (Tuesday, November 9, 1982): Scouts plan honor for long time leader; (Monday, December 20, 1982): New Yale Program: A Matter of Degrees (Box 82, Folder 110)
    - Staff Day (Box 82, Folder 111)
    - Stiles, Ezra (Box 82, Folder 112)
    - Summer Term
      - 1974-1975 (Box 82, Folder 113)
      - 1976 (Box 82, Folder 114)
      - 1977 (Box 82, Folder 115)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 83, Folder 116)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 83, Folder 117)
      - 1985-1988 (Box 83, Folder 118)
    - Summer Film Series, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 119)
    - Taft, William H., Plaque Ceremony, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 120)
    - Telephone System (Box 83, Folder 121)
    - Tree Planting, 1970s (Box 83, Folder 122 - 123)
    - Trumbull College, Press, 1978 (Box 83, Folder 124)
    - Tutoring Program (Box 83, Folder 125)
    - University Council: Arbiters of Excellence, 1990 summer (Box 83, Folder 126)
    - University Printing Services, Dinosaur Poster, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 127)
    - United Way
      - 1980-1982 (Box 84, Folder 128)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 84, Folder 129)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 84, Folder 130 - 131)
      - 1987 (Box 84, Folder 132)
      - 1988 (Box 84, Folder 133)
      - 1989 (Box 84, Folder 134)
      - 1990 (Box 85, Folder 135)
      - 1991 (Box 85, Folder 136)
    - Write-in-Residence Program, 1990 (Box 85, Folder 137)
    - Yale College
      - "Early Action" (Box 85, Folder 138)
      - Internship Program (Box 85, Folder 139)
      - Prizes (Box 85, Folder 140)
    - Yale Glee Club, Organ Fund (Box 85, Folder 141)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine, George Pierson: How Yale really began, 1988 November (Box 85, Folder 142)
    - Yale Daily News (Box 85, Folder 143)
    - Yale Political Union (Box 85, Folder 144)
    - Yale Russian Chorus (Box 85, Folder 145)
    - Yale Symphony Orchestra (Box 85, Folder 146)
    - Yale University Bands (Box 85, Folder 147)
  - Alumni
    - Alumni Fund
    - Convocation
      - 1977 September (Box 86, Folder 148)
      - 1978 October (Box 86, Folder 149)
      - 1979 October (Box 86, Folder 150 - 151)
      - 90th Year, 1980 October (Box 86, Folder 152)
      - 1981 October (Box 86, Folder 153)
      - 1982 October (Box 86, Folder 154)
      - 1983 October (Box 86, Folder 155)
      - 1984 October (Box 86, Folder 156)
      - 1985 October (Box 86, Folder 157)
      - 1986 October (Box 86, Folder 158)
      - 1988 October (Box 86, Folder 159)
    - Staff (Box 86, Folder 160)
    - Class Agents, Medical School (Box 86, Folder 161)
    - 1991 September (Box 86, Folder 162)
    - Greenwich, CT, 1978 April 25 (Box 86, Folder 163)
    - Individual and Small Groups of Staff (Box 86, Folder 164)
    - Directors, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 165)
    - Group Photo, 1990 June (Box 86, Folder 166)
    - 100th Anniversary, 1990 November (Box 86, Folder 167 - 168)
    - Meeting (Box 86, Folder 169)
    - Parents Program, 1987 September (Box 86, Folder 170)
  - Awards
    - Miscellaneous (Box 87, Folder 171)
    - Bilder Awards, 1978-1989 (Box 87, Folder 172)
    - Bollingen Prize in Poetry, 1987-1989 (Box 87, Folder 173)
    - Community Service Awards, undated (Box 87, Folder 174)
    - Community Service Awards, 1989-1992 (Box 87, Folder 175)
    - Elm-Ivy Awards, 1980- 1987 (Box 87, Folder 176)
    - Elm-Ivy, Sterling, Shafer, 1988-1992 (Box 87, Folder 177)
    - Field Prize, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 178)
    - Jefferson Award for Public Service, 1990 April (Box 87, Folder 179)
    - Lohmann Prize, 1981-1988 (Box 87, Folder 180)
    - NSF, PYI, 1987-1992 (Box 87, Folder 181)
    - Scholastic Achievement Award, 1984 (Box 87, Folder 182)
    - Yale Scientific Magazine Awards, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 183)
    - Steedman Traveling Fellowship, 1979 (Box 87, Folder 184)
    - Student Humanitarian Award, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 185)
    - Student Volunteers Award, Robinson-Freedman Service Award, 1988 (Box 87, Folder 186)
    - U.S. Marine Corps, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 187)
    - Van Sinderen Prize, 1988 (Box 87, Folder 188)
    - Yale Art Awards for Outstanding Achievement, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 189)
  - Buildings
    - Aerials (Box 88, Folder 190)
    - Ana-Arm (Box 88, Folder 191)
    - Art-Bat (Box 88, Folder 192)
    - Bec-Bei (Box 88, Folder 193)
    - Ber (Box 88, Folder 194)
    - Bio-Bra (Box 89, Folder 195)
    - Ber-Bin (Box 89, Folder 196)
    - Cal-Col (Box 89, Folder 197)
    - Com-Con (Box 89, Folder 198)
    - Cox-Cro (Box 89, Folder 199)
    - Dai-Dav (Box 89, Folder 200)
    - Div-Dra (Box 90, Folder 201)
    - Dun-Epi (Box 90, Folder 202)
    - Fac-Gra (Box 90, Folder 203)
    - Gra-Gre (Box 90, Folder 204)
    - Gyp-Har (Box 90, Folder 205)
    - HarknessTower (Box 90, Folder 206 - 207)
    - Health Services (Box 91, Folder 208)
    - Hen-Hil (Box 91, Folder 209)
    - Hil-Ing (Box 91, Folder 210)
    - Ins-Jon (Box 91, Folder 211)
    - Kin-Lap (Box 91, Folder 212)
    - Law School (Box 91, Folder 213)
    - Law-Mas (Box 91, Folder 214)
    - Mem-Nur (Box 92, Folder 215)
    - Old Campus (Box 92, Folder 216 - 219)
    - Old-Pay (Box 92, Folder 220)
    - Pea-Pie (Box 93, Folder 221)
    - Pol-Ren (Box 93, Folder 222)
    - Ros-Say (Box 93, Folder 223)
    - Sci-See (Box 93, Folder 224)
    - She-Spr (Box 93, Folder 225)
    - SSS-Ste (Box 94, Folder 226)
    - Sterling Memorial Library (Box 94, Folder 227)
    - Ste-Sto (Box 94, Folder 228)
    - Str-Tim (Box 94, Folder 229)
    - Tru-Van (Box 94, Folder 230)
    - Wat-Whi (Box 95, Folder 231)
    - Whi-Wil (Box 95, Folder 232)
    - Win-Wri (Box 95, Folder 233)
    - Yal-Yor (Box 95, Folder 234)
  - Campaign for Yale
    - Announcement, 1974 April 8 (Box 96, Folder 235)
    - Campaign Buttons, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 236)
    - Chicago Meeting, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 237)
    - General, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 238)
    - New York City, Board Meeting, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 239)
    - Executive Meeting, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 240)
    - Greater New Haven Area, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 241)
    - Muyskens, Regional Office, West Coast, 1976 (Box 96, Folder 242)
    - Telephone Group, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 243)
    - Volunteers, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 244)
    - Brochure, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 245)
    - The Yale Campaign
      - Pre-Campaign Tour, 1991 September (Box 97, Folder 246)
      - Launch (Box 97, Folder 247)
      - Launch and AYA Assembly (Box 97, Folder 248)
      - Campaign (Box 97, Folder 249)
  - Commencement
    - 1950s, 1961, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 250)
    - 1974 (Box 98, Folder 251 - 252)
    - 1975 (Box 98, Folder 253)
    - 1976 (Box 98, Folder 254 - 255)
    - 1977 (Box 98, Folder 256 - 258)
    - 1978 (Box 99, Folder 259 - 261)
    - 1979 (Box 99, Folder 262 - 264)
    - 1980 (Box 100, Folder 265)
    - 1981 (Box 100, Folder 266 - 268)
    - 1982 (Box 100, Folder 269 - 275)
    - 1983 (Box 101, Folder 276 - 279)
    - 1984 (Box 101, Folder 280 - 282)
    - 1984 (Box 102, Folder 283 - 285)
    - 1985 (Box 102, Folder 286 - 292)
    - 1986 (Box 103, Folder 293 - 298)
    - 1987 (Box 103, Folder 299 - 301)
    - 1987 (Box 104, Folder 302 - 307)
    - 1988 (Box 104, Folder 308 - 314)
    - 1988 (Box 105, Folder 315 - 323)
    - 1989 (Box 106, Folder 324 - 332)
  - Freshman Class Arrivals
    - Class of 1978-1979, Yale Alumni Magazine: The Freshman Class, 1978 October (Box 107, Folder 333)
    - Class of 1980-1981 (Box 107, Folder 334)
    - Class of 1982 (Box 107, Folder 335)
    - Class of 1983-1984 (Box 107, Folder 336)
    - Class of 1985 (Box 107, Folder 337)
    - Class of 1986-1987 (Box 108, Folder 338)
    - Class of 1990 (Box 108, Folder 339)
    - Class of 1991-1992 (Box 108, Folder 340)
    - Class of 1993-1994 (Box 108, Folder 341)
  - Scenic views
    - 1970s (Box 109, Folder 342 - 343)
    - 1980s (Box 109, Folder 344 - 346)
    - Ice Storm, 1984 (Box 109, Folder 347)
    - 1985 (Box 109, Folder 348)
    - 1986 (Box 109, Folder 349)
    - 1987 (Box 110, Folder 350)
    - 1988 (Box 110, Folder 351)
    - 1988 December (Box 110, Folder 352)
    - 1989 (Box 110, Folder 353)
    - Tornado Damage, 1989 (Box 110, Folder 354)
  - Scholarships
    - Scholars of the House, 1977-1985 (Box 111, Folder 355)
    - Graduate School, Young Leaders Fellowship, 1990 (Box 111, Folder 356)
    - Marshall Scholars, 1985-1991 (Box 111, Folder 357)
    - Miss Black Connecticut, 1992 (Box 111, Folder 358)
    - Morse Scholar, 1990 (Box 111, Folder 359)
    - Yale Club of New York Scholarships (Box 111, Folder 360)
    - Pew Scholars, 1987 (Box 111, Folder 361)
    - Rhodes Scholars
      - 1978, 1980, 1984, 1986, 1988 (Box 111, Folder 362)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 111, Folder 363)
    - Yale Club of New York Scholarships, 1988-1991 (Box 111, Folder 364)